<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description></description>
    <link>help.beegit.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="help.beegit.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>What is the dashboard?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-the-dashboard&quot;&gt;What is the dashboard?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dashboard is your landing place when you log into Beegit and it allows you to view your projects and collaborators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You enter on your project list, which shows all of the projects you own or are a collaborator on. From your dashboard you can switch to the global collaborators list, which shows all the collaborators added to projects you own. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a new user without any projects, your dashboard will be blank. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-project-dashboard&quot;&gt;The project dashboard&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your project dashboard shows every project you’re on, sorted by owner. If you own all of your projects, you’ll just see your name in the right-hand navigation. If you are on projects with several owners, you can sort through the list of owners on the right-hand side to view projects by each owner. You’ll always see the project owner you’re viewing at the top of the dashboard. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/beegit-images/helpImages/dashboard-list.png&quot; alt=&quot;Dashboard List&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within the project owner view, you’ll be able to sort and search the project list to easily find what you want to work on. After you’ve worked on a project for an owner, the dashboard will be set to that owner’s projects the next time you log in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;collaborator-list&quot;&gt;Collaborator list&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can switch to your global collaborator list on the dashboard to view all your collaborators. This list shows people with whom you collaborate on projects you own. If you only collaborate on other people’s projects, this list will be empty. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are a project owner, you can use this collaborator list to set default teams or groups to be added to new projects or to manage notification settings for your collaborators. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-is-the-dashboard</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-is-the-dashboard</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Markdown?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-markdown&quot;&gt;What is Markdown?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is a plain text formatting syntax designed so that it optionally can be converted to HTML. Markdown is growing in popularity across the web for its flexibility and for its ability to format text once so that it can be used in multiple display outlets. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beegit uses Markdown for its simplicity and the extensibility it offers to export to not just HTML, but also print formats like Word and InDesign. We use a flavor called PageDown. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-is-markdown</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-is-markdown</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Beegit?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-beegit&quot;&gt;What is Beegit?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beegit is a content-first project management solution for large and small teams. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It helps users understand how their content team works and how it can work better by centralizing everything in one place, a collaborative web editor with light workflow tools. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teams can write on the web in a simple version control system and @mention teammates when content is ready for review or production. To keep the content adaptive, everything is formatted in Markdown, which is ready for common print and web formats. To make the team even better, the system produces some basic metrics on who did what during the project.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-is-beegit</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-is-beegit</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is a version?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-version&quot;&gt;What is a version?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything you type in Beegit’s editor is autosaved as you work. But when you’re at a stopping point, you can make a version that will exist in the project forever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A version is like a milestone or a hand-off point in your work. When you create a version, you’ll be able to leave a note for yourself or others describing what you’ve done. You can even @mention specific people on the project so they get an email notification about this version. Before you make your version, you can review the differences on every file you touched. They’ll show words that you added highlighted in green and words that you deleted highlighted in red. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you commit a version, it’s in the system forever and you’ll always be able to go back and look at the changes, the note and the files and folders as they existed at that time. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-is-a-version</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-is-a-version</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is a README?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-readme&quot;&gt;What is a README?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A README file is included with the creation of every project in Beegit and is meant to contain information about other files and folders inside the project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;README’s are commonly used as writing prompts, overviews of the project or a shared knowledge space for collaborators on the project. Updates to your README will be included in your version history. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-is-a-readme</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-is-a-readme</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is a project?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-project&quot;&gt;What is a project?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A project is a place to organize all your content, communications and insight around an objective, goal or deadline. A project could be an issue of a publication, copy for a client, content for a website or a shared document.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/getting%20started/2014/11/01/what-is-a-project/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/getting%20started/2014/11/01/what-is-a-project/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is a collaborator?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-a-collaborator&quot;&gt;What is a collaborator?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A collaborator is someone who works on any project with you. If you’re the owner of a project, you can set their user roles to observer, editor or admin. You can also decide on their default email notification settings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been invited to a project, your user role has been set by the project owner. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;making-a-project-team&quot;&gt;Making a project team&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have a team you work with on every project you own, you can set those users to automatically be added to every new project you create in the global collaborators section on your dashboard. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;adding-collaborators-to-a-project&quot;&gt;Adding collaborators to a project&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there are collaborators you only want to involve in certain projects, add them using the global collaborator section on your dashboard. Set their role and then choose no when asked if you want to add them to every project. After you add that user, they will be available on your global collaborator list and you can invite them to any specific project inside that project’s collaborator section.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-is-a-collaborator</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-is-a-collaborator</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What happens after I cancel my subscription?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-happens-after-i-cancel-my-subscription&quot;&gt;What happens after I cancel my subscription?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canceled subscriptions stay active until the next billing cycle date. After that, you will not be charged again and your subscription will be put in observer mode on that date. This means your files will be read-only and you will no longer be able to write or edit in the system. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you cancel, your billing page will indicate that the subscription will be canceled by displaying the following message in red: “Your subscription is set to cancel on MM/DD/YYYY.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-happens-after-i-cancel-my-subscription</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-happens-after-i-cancel-my-subscription</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What are files and folders?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-files-and-folders&quot;&gt;What are files and folders?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Files and folders are the fundamental elements of the files section. They can be easily created, renamed and deleted using the icons in the file toolbar above the file tree. Files and folders can be nested via drag and drop. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;working-with-files&quot;&gt;Working with files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Files are documents that you create inside of a project. They are meant to be used with your normal organization workflow, acting as a single document for an entire project or as one of several documents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/beegit-images/helpImages/editor-drag-drop.png&quot; alt=&quot;Editor Drag and Drop&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;working-with-folders&quot;&gt;Working with folders&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Folders help you organize your work inside Beegit. You can name them and store files or nest other folders inside of them. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-are-files-and-folders</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-are-files-and-folders</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What are content metrics?</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-are-content-metrics&quot;&gt;What are content metrics?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inside your project, you’ll find a tab called Metrics. These metrics are a quick weekly overview of your project progress. They show you how much work has been done in terms of hours spent by your team in Beegit’s editor and how many words were added and deleted during that time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/beegit-images/helpImages/metrics-everyone.png&quot; alt=&quot;Metrics Everyone&quot; /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can filter this information even further by hitting the Group by User toggle, which will display the metric information by what each user contributed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s3.amazonaws.com/beegit-images/helpImages/metrics-user.png&quot; alt=&quot;Metrics User&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>help.beegit.com/what-are-content-metrics</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">help.beegit.com/what-are-content-metrics</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
